[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":150763,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":168971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":12617,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":181597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":19628,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":201230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":27218,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":228457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":12179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":240643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1762,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":242415,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you  subtract  6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7892,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":250311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1374,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":251690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":256165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct ! 1 +<su b>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":986,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":257156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["0","3"],"rt":138079,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":395240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1020,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":396270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub> 6</sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5625,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":401899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":938,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":402841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":406398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":957,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":407359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2773,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":410136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1129,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":411269,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":10878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":422152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1415,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":423572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If  the sum  is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2270,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":425845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":821,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":426670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":23188,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":449868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":51028,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":500903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3930,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":504840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":28647,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":533493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6062,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":539564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2033,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":541602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3202,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":544807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4021,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":548832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2678,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":551514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5696,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":557214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3107,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":560325,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1463,"trial_type":"feedb ack","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":561793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":8027,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":569823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under  +<sub>6 </sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":2550,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":572377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":579077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":978,"trial_type":"fee dback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":580061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":581815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":951,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":582769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":585788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":828,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":586619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":2481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":589104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":28409,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":617516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sur e you un derstand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":2796,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":620316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"45","response_history":["45"],"rt":5367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":625689,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":7037,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":632735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":635405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":639931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":2635,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":642570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2366,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":644941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["12","1","1","3"],"rt":10191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":655138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4 ","response_history":["4 "],"rt":7622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":662767,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4 = 12","response_history":["5 I ","5 I","5 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4+","5 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4 = 12","1 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4 = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4 = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4+ = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4+4 = 12","12 , 4 i s the in verse of 4 so 8 + 4+ = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4 = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4- = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4-4 = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4- = 12","12 , 4 is the inverse of 4 so 8 + 4 = 12"],"rt":48165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":710938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"+0 because it needs an identity to know what it is.","response_history":["+0 f","+0 because ie","+0 because it needs an identity to know what it is."],"rt":17677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":728623,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"5","response_history":["-","5"],"rt":80439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":809070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":812572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":815926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 I think inverse would be the same number repeated","response_history":["3 I think inverse would be the same number repeated"],"rt":11655,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":827586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4 is a generator which is 2+2.","response_history":["4 is a generator which is 2+2."],"rt":17365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":844960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3+3 is +g. To be honest, I was lost throughout the lesson and forgot what eactly the symbol means.","response_history":["3+3 is +g. D","3+3 is +g. To be honest ","3+3 is +g. To be honest, I was lost throughout the lesson and forg o ","3+3  is +g. To be honest, I was lost throughout the lesson and forgot what goes on.","3+3 is +g. To be honest, I was lost throughout the lesson and forgot what eacf","3+3 is +g. To be honest, I was lost throughout the lesson and forgot what eactly the symbol means."],"rt":148622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":993590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because is it less than 6.","response_history":["5+5","N","No, because it","No, because is it less than 6."],"rt":17969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1011575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":" Yes because it is 6 or higher.","response_history":["Yes because it is 6 of hi","Yes because it is 6 of h","Yes because it is 6 of ","Yes because it is 6 of","Yes because it is 6 or higher."],"rt":9661,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1021244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":8228,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1029476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+1","response_history":["1+1"],"rt":8222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1037705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"+x whatever the number x is, is also n.","response_history":["+x+","+x whatever the number is ","+x whatever the number is","+x whatever the number i","+x whatever the number x is is ","+x whatever the number x is is","+x whatever the number x is i","+x whatever the number x is ","+x whatever the number x is, is also n ","+x whatever the number x is, is also n."],"rt":19659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1057374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether  it can  make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"+n is the positive number. No.","response_history":["+n is a","+n is the next ","+n is the next","+n is the nex","+n is the ne","+n is the n","+n is the postive number. No.","+n is the positive number. No."],"rt":17792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1075174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":2293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1077476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1080067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":1664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1081735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Because you need both values to know the formula. ","response_history":["Because you need both numbers","Because you need both number","Because you need both  numbe"," Because you need both numb","Because you need both num","Because you need both nu","Because you need both n","Because you need both ","Because you need both","Because you need bot","Because you need bo","Because you need b","Because you need to ","Because you need to","Because you need t","Because you need both values to know the c","Because you need both values to know the probme ","Because you need both values to know the probme","Because you need both values to know the probm","Because you need both values to know the prob","Because you need both values to know the pro","Because you need both values to know the pr","Because you need both values to know the p","Because you need both values to know the ","Because you need both values to know thefor","Because you need both values to know thefo","Because you need both values to know thef ","Because you need both values to know thef","Because you need both values to know the forum","Because you need both values to know the for ula. "," Because you need both values to know the formula. "],"rt":100430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1182170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":2717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1184896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from wh at i've  learned it could apply to multiple things.","response_history":["Soe","Sometimes. I am saythin","Sometimes. I am saythi","Sometimes. I am sayth","Sometimes. I am sayt","Sometimes. I am saying soeme","Sometimes. I am saying soem","Sometimes. I am saying soe","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to mulitp","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to mulit","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to muli","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to multiplt ","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to multiplt","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel li ke from  what ive learned it could apply to multiple things/ ","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to multiple things/","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what ive learned it could apply to multiple things.","Sometimes. I am saying sometimes because i am lost at this point and I feel like from what i've learned it could apply to multiple things."],"rt":46280,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1231182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":17521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1248714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1795,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1250515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"21","response_history":["21"],"rt":2468,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1252988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1256212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Pre-trig.","response_history":["A","Ag","Aleb","Ale","Al","A","Pre tr","Pre t","Pre ","Pre","Pre-trig."],"rt":16378,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1272595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["1 - never heard of i t","2 -  heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4561,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1277164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1281239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somew hat"],"rt":2736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1283979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2153,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1286137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1288275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Mal e","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1290184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English ","English, Pani","English, Pan","English, Pa","English, P","English, ","English,","English","English"],"rt":7489,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1297676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3383,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1301067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was very hard, thank you though.","response_history":["This was very hard, thank you though."],"rt":6651,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1307723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]